foreign
for 10 years
and
your you could make sense and you repent
but you cannot be forgiven
and then all of a sudden you come from
the realization that you should not be
an eyes and worshiper and come out of
either watches and all your sins
and be forgiven and confesses the
credits
just go to
this is the description of the believer
63 let's start at 63 page 249 763 just
and for the Servants of the most
versions to walk on earth humbly and
when the ignorant speak to them the only
utter peace and who spent the night
before the Lord frustrating and standing
and who say our most experience the
enemy of the enemies suddenly its
resolution is organizing it is
I want to extend we are neither
extravagant nor thingy your mother
and they never set up the price to have
any idea nor do they kill anyone except
in the course of Justice nor do they
commit adultery anyone who does this is
working
foreign
you continue to repent
but be ready to go every time and make
sure that you are skinless
depending all the time
and if you are performing same thing
you'll be ready to pay if you think this
is wrong and you're going to do it
anyway
you're ready to pray
the way this word is conjoined the
phrase work righteousness is conjoined
with dependence
in 1771
maybe the suggestion and often is that
suppose you harm
someone
and therefore you have disobeyed Allah
and you ask Allah for forgiveness for
what you have done but still this might
not be enough we have to work
righteousness you might have to make
amend regarding the prayer from whom
because I know the Quran is always put
belief and work together always together
because I I do remember
years ago there's this problem was
discussed in our country
and our teachers one of the street man
he said
if you insult the man
how few things to say
if that man really is repentance and he
meant what he said it is not Allah I'm
sorry that I saw this man he should go
to this man in a couple of times and and
that is doing what Allah wants him to do
so there is
the social aspect this this mother also
brings both of the importance of the
duties
also the five prayers today and the
customers
obviously those aren't God is trying to
help us wipe out all the sins
it's another
answer to the question why should we
pray Christ
because of the inadvertent things that
can do around because of the days in it
because of the things
so all the the players and crafting and
these things provided
but this is the one who go to heaven you
will not have all those things that were
attended come on we don't have any
records unless we do a person
investigation in your own but we will
start to see we're gonna try and go back
and deliver your life and birth to death
you will do it you can do it if you want
but nobody answers you because it's
already
thank you
and everything you get anything you want
if you want to look back and do your
life only you can do it if you don't
want anybody else to see it under you if
you decide that you're gonna win the
kingdom of God God says you do whatever
you want
it's absolutely no embarrassment no
uh humidation
there's always there's nothing but
dignity and happiness and love and
purpose it's the perfection
because
these are the means of editing the faith
repentance
and right before
okay back to our lesson
Johnny and pepper and pastor 21. verse
and I was experience or the things that
we do
over your body
because
the vast majority of people the body is
the ball
they do everything in this life to
please the body to give it a good job
good money good house good sounds
the body whatever they cater to the
body's desire that's all they want
that's all they do
it is the most stupid thing anybody can
do so the body vanity becomes dust
and then you stand by yourself
you know people you can imagine the
person after setting the body they say
my God I spent all my life caring for
this thing since he's dropping now
then I went to school drug test
to get a good degree and have a good job
I just kept my life caring for this
thing what did I do for myself
now what you do to yourself for yourself
is
the spiritual tools Superior suggestions
worshiping God remembering that
because your son is part of that
I think you are able to suffering some
head injury then you may cut your hair
and that's by it by fasting or giving a
charity or some other form of work
sacrifice
when we were making had my father wanted
to break the
code
between Omron and had but it makes it
really was very early
you were there on the first day of the
of the month
and then the day the official value of
parts of the earthquake everybody must
be invested
let's this is the very of course
on tonight's day everybody must be a
mouse out of us so we went on the first
to finish download the first now we have
eight days and my father wanted to relax
changes close to everyone he wanted to
do so he had to sacrifice his team
and this was this first day
I told not Progressive
okay
yeah can you go to college the
requirements like
did you say Santa Claus
but most of the practices come to us
like Whoever has go away but actually
most of the has been mentioned here
you know the encircleaning of guitar
Expressions here
the United States
where can I please
foreign
that's why the language of the Quran is
very important here in Arabic what God
says it is certainly all right to go
around the child you are not committing
Yourself by inserting the cover this is
the other day
the night with the Quran is very it's
not God said it's going to be alive for
you to support Prospect before Adam
Adam
or what so it is by permission to God
to God
and the answer for another month because
they worshiped in obedience to God
and
that's the language is very very careful
and very insignificant
so if anybody tells you that this is a
problem by the Washington State
Bank it's all right
the specific question that you are not
committing at him bye let me see
two or three
you can't remember that goddamn specific
questions